<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Art Space</string>
    <string name="title">Top Uncensored Anime</string>
    <string name="highdchooldxd">The storyline follows Issei Hyodo, a second year student living a peaceful life at the KuOh Academy. The academy isn’t any ordinary one because it has angels, fallen angels and demons intermixed with students. After an ordinary day at the academy Issei is asked out on a date by Yuma Amano.\n\nAfter the date, she reveals to him that she’s a fallen angel and tries to kill Issei, when Rias Gremory, a third year student saves his life. But when he wakes up the next day, Issei finds out that Rias is a devil and that she’s saved Issei’s life by turning him into one as well. And thus the interesting story continues.</string>
    <string name="highSchoolOfTheDead">The story begins at Fujimi High School, where students are going about their daily lives when a mysterious pandemic suddenly turns people into aggressive, flesh-eating zombies (referred to as \"Them\"). The school is quickly overrun, and chaos ensues as students and staff are attacked and infected.</string>
    <string name="Freezing">The story takes place in a future where Earth is under constant threat from interdimensional beings called Nova. These creatures are highly destructive and can only be fought by genetically enhanced female warriors known as Pandoras, who are paired with male partners called Limiters. Limiters use a special ability called Freezing to slow down the Nova and support the Pandoras in battle.</string>
    <string name="PrisonSchool">The story takes place at Hachimitsu Academy, a prestigious all-girls school that has recently opened its doors to male students. However, the male population is tiny compared to the female student body, creating a highly imbalanced environment. The school is run by a strict and oppressive student council that enforces harsh rules, particularly on the male students.\n</string>
    <string name="DomesticGirlfriend">The story begins with Natsuo attending a mixer in an attempt to get over his unrequited crush on his teacher, Hina Tachibana. At the mixer, he meets Rui Tachibana, a quiet and reserved girl who proposes they lose their virginity to each other. The two share a one-night stand, but they part ways afterward, thinking they’ll never see each other again.</string>
    <string name="DemonKingDiamao">In a world where magic is an integral part of daily life, individuals train to become powerful mages or influential leaders. Akuto Sai, the protagonist, enrolls at Constant Magic Academy, a prestigious institution that prepares students for roles such as heroes, priests, or even the Demon King.</string>
    <string name="HaremInTheLabyrinthOfAnotherWorld">The protagonist, Michio Kaga, is a young man from modern-day Japan who finds himself transported to this fantasy world. Upon arrival, he discovers that he has access to a unique ability called the \"Browser\" function, which allows him to view and manipulate his status, skills, and inventory like a video game menu. This gives him a significant advantage in navigating the world and its challenges.</string>
    <string name="BladeofTheImmortal">Manji is a ronin (masterless samurai) who has been cursed with immortality after killing 100 innocent people. To atone for his sins, he vows to kill 1,000 evil men in the hope that this will lift his curse and allow him to die. His life takes a dramatic turn when he encounters Rin Asano, a young girl seeking revenge against the Itto-ryu, a group of rogue swordsmen who murdered her parents.\n\n</string>
    <string name="MonsterMusume">The protagonist, Kimihito Kurusu, is a kind-hearted young man who accidentally becomes involved in the exchange program when a liminal named Miia, a lamia (half-human, half-snake), is sent to live with him. Despite his initial shock, Kimihito agrees to host Miia, and his life quickly becomes chaotic as more liminals join his household.\n\nOver time, Kimihito\'s home becomes a haven for various monster girls, each with their own unique traits and personalities:</string>
    <string name="MonsterGirlDoctor">The protagonist, Dr. Glenn Litbeit, is a skilled and compassionate human physician who specializes in treating monster girls. Alongside his assistant, Saphentite (Sapphee) Neikes, a lamia (half-human, half-snake) who is also his childhood friend and fiancée, Glenn runs a clinic dedicated to providing medical care to liminals.\n\nEach episode or chapter focuses on Glenn and Sapphee treating different monster girl patients, addressing their unique medical conditions and challenges.</string>
</resources>